<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ernest</title>
    <link>http://docs.ernest.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ernest</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://docs.ernest.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Setup Ernest In this quickstart guide we will build a simple environment consisting of a public server and private server on AWS, and allow SSH access from our IP. You will need a working copy of Ernest and the Ernest CLI, your AWS Access Key and Secret Key.
Get Ernest Follow the instructions here to get Ernest and the Ernest CLI.
Setup Your User Target your Ernest instance:
$ ernest target https://10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commands</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/commands/</guid>
      <description>Using the CLI Connecting to Ernest First specify the IP address of our Ernest Server:
$ ernest target https://&amp;lt;Ernest Server IP&amp;gt; Target set  Now we should login to Ernest with the built-in admin account:
$ ernest login Username: admin Password: *******  Projects Ernest uses the concept of a project to group together one or more environments. A project can specify the default infrastructure service provider for those projects, although this can be overriden on at the environment level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providers</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/providers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/providers/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Web Services Amazon Web Services (AWS) is a secure cloud services platform, offering compute power, database storage, content delivery and other functionality to help businesses scale and grow.
The following AWS services are supported by Ernest:
 EC2 VPC ELB S3 Route53 RDS EBS IAM  Example YAML --- name: demo project: my-dc vpcs: - name: my-vpc id: vpc-abcdef01 subnet: 10.0.0.0/16 auto_remove: true networks: - name: web subnet: 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Using the CLI Connecting to Ernest The first step is to specify the IP address of our Ernest Server:
$ ernest target https://&amp;lt;Ernest Server IP&amp;gt; Target set  Now we should login to Ernest with the built-in admin account:
$ ernest login Username: admin Password: *******  (The default admin password is ‘w4rmR3d’)
and change the admin password:
$ ernest user change-password You&#39;re about to change your password, please respond the questions below: Current password: &amp;lt;old admin password&amp;gt; New password: &amp;lt;new admin password&amp;gt; Confirm new password: &amp;lt;new admin password&amp;gt; Your password has been changed  Now we can create a user, a group, and add the user to the group:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Get Ernest Below are instructions for installing the latest stable release of Ernest (Release Notes).
Requirements: Docker, Docker Compose, OpenSSL.
Community Edition  Clone the repo containing the setup file: git clone https://github.com/ernestio/ernest.git
 Change to the cloned directory: cd ernest
 Run the setup script: ./setup
 Enter the hostname, admin username, and admin password when prompted.
  Once the install is finished Ernest will be available on IP of the Docker host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/developer/</guid>
      <description>Architecture overview Ernest is based on a microservice oriented architecture. The majority of the services are built using Go, however we still need to maintain some jruby based in order to interact with vCloud.
Naming conventions In order to keep it clean there are some naming conventions you need to follow in order to understand Ernest
Service Naming Every service family follows an easy to understand naming convention.
Connectors A connector name will look like component-action-provider-component.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/community/</guid>
      <description>Discuss To discuss all things Ernest with other members of the community:
 join the Ernest Slack channel join the Ernest Google Group  Contribute Ernest, the Ernest CLI, the VSE Creator Service, and the Ernest Site (this website) are all open source projects under the Mozilla Public License v2.0. If you would like to help us improve these projects you can do so here:
  Project Name Contribute Code Request a Feature Report a Bug     Ernest GitHub GitHub Issue GitHub Issue   Ernest CLI GitHub GitHub Issue GitHub Issue   Ernest Site GitHub GitHub Issue GitHub Issue    Social Follow us on Twitter and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/support/</guid>
      <description>R3 Labs offer two support plans for Ernest:
    Standard Premium     Contract Type Annual subscription Annual subscription   Access to a technical support website &amp;#x25cf; &amp;#x25cf;   Maintenance and upgrades &amp;#x25cf; &amp;#x25cf;   Web support (email/chat) during standard business hours (9:00AM – 5:00 PM CET) &amp;#x25cf; &amp;#x25cf;   Maximum number of designated contacts 1 3   Feature priorities  &amp;#x25cf;   Prioritized issue resolution  &amp;#x25cf;   Response time on non-critical issues Best effort Within 8 business hours   Response time on critical issues** Within 8 business hours Within 4 hours   Pricing Contact us Contact us    **A ‘Critical Issue’ is defined as a system down that impacts your use of Ernest in a production environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Public License Version 2.0</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/license/</guid>
      <description>1. Definitions 1.1. “Contributor” means each individual or legal entity that creates, contributes to the creation of, or owns Covered Software.
1.2. “Contributor Version” means the combination of the Contributions of others (if any) used by a Contributor and that particular Contributor’s Contribution.
1.3. “Contribution” means Covered Software of a particular Contributor.
1.4. “Covered Software” means Source Code Form to which the initial Contributor has attached the notice in Exhibit A, the Executable Form of such Source Code Form, and Modifications of such Source Code Form, in each case including portions thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Plan Contact Form</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/supportplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/supportplan/</guid>
      <description>  First Name  Last Name  Email Address  Support Plan  Standard    Premium     Submit    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vCloud Account Creation Request Form</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/vcloud-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/vcloud-account/</guid>
      <description>  First Name  Last Name  Email Address   Submit    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Slack Channel Access Form</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/slack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 19:56:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/slack/</guid>
      <description>  First Name:   Last Name:   Email Address:     Submit     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ernest</title>
      <link>http://docs.ernest.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://docs.ernest.io/</guid>
      <description>Overview Ernest is an application and infrastructure orchestration and automation engine. Ernest takes the complexity and people out of DevOps, simplifying the process of creating and managing even the most complex environments.
By delivering everything a development team requires to be able to deploy code and manage its lifecycle Ernest de-risks and accelerates the application development/deployment process, helping developers to deliver value back to the business faster and providing increased business agility</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>